One rectangle of construction paper
Make the center crease
Open the sheet again
Left edge to the center
Right edge to the center
Fan the right flap outward
Fan the left flap outward
Fold the upper-right corner
Fold the upper-left corner
Turn the paper over
Bring the top point to the bottom
Fold the small right shoulder
Fold the small left shoulder
Lift the point over the small corners
Turn over to expose the small point
Fold the small exposed point down
Close the model along its center
Fold the first wing, keeping a body strip
Fold the matching wing on the other side
Open the wings into flying position
Your finished flying bat — all sides